♪
( ax chops )
Boy: 47.
( boy #2 sighs )
( ax chops )
( boy #1 panting )
AND 50!
( gasps )
Boy #2: OUT OF 50 CHOPS,
I ONLY HEARD
THREE GOOD ONES THERE.
SO FAR, THAT BRINGS
YOUR TOTAL TO 41.
SORRY, EUGEO.
LOOKS LIKE THE SIRAL WATER’S
ON YOU AGAIN.
Eugeo: OH, WHATEVER. YOU GOT
WHAT, 43 GOOD CHOPS SO FAR?
I’LL CATCH UP SOON.
GO ON. IT’S YOUR TURN
AT THE AX, KIRITO.
Kirito: YEAH, IN A SEC.
EVERY DAY, FOR THE PAST YEAR
AND THREE MONTHS,
WE’VE BEEN HACKIN’ AWAY
AT THIS DARN TREE.
I CAN’T TAKE IT ANY MORE.
Eugeo: THERE’S NO USE
COMPLAINING ABOUT IT.
OUR CALLING’S TO CUT
THE GIGAS CEDAR DOWN,
SO THERE’S
NO GETTING OUT OF IT.
Kirito: YEAH, I KNOW
YOU’RE RIGHT, BUT, STILL,
DOESN’T FEEL LIKE
WE’RE GETTING ANYWHERE.
THAT’S ITS LIFE NOW.
WHAT WAS IT TWO MONTHS AGO?
Eugeo: I THINK IT WAS AT...
235,590?
Kirito: I’M GONNA BE SICK.
AFTER TWO MONTHS
OF CHOPPING AT IT,
WE ONLY GOT ITS LIFE DOWN
A LOUSY 50?!
( moans ) IT’S GONNA TAKE US
FOREVER TO CUT IT DOWN!
( Eugeo laughs )
WHAT’D YOU EXPECT?
THIS TREE’S AS STRONG AS STEEL.
SIX GENERATIONS OF CARVERS
WORKED ON IT FOR 300 YEARS
TO GET THIS FAR.
IT’LL GET CUT DOWN...
IN 900 YEARS OR SO.
Kirito: OH, IS THAT ALL?
WELL...
( both grunting )
Eugeo: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Kirito: YOU THINK
YOU’RE SUCH A SMARTY-PANTS!
WHY DON’T YOU USE
THAT BIG BRAIN OF YOURS
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET US OUT OF THIS JOB?
Eugeo: WOULD YOU--
STOP IT!
GET OFF!
- NOW IT’S MY TURN.
- ( Kirito laughing )
Eugeo: HOW DO YOU
LIKE THAT, HUH?!
WANT MORE, OR DO YOU GIVE UP?
- WHOA!
- Kirito: NOT EVEN!
- PAYBACK TIME!
- ( Eugeo laughing )
Kirito: NO SURRENDER!
Eugeo: NO! STOP IT!
Kirito: NOPE!
Girl: I KNEW I’D FIND
YOU BOYS GOOFING OFF!
Kirito: DANG IT.
Eugeo: OH. H-HI, ALICE.
Kirito: DID YOUR SACRED ARTS
CLASS LET OUT EARLY TODAY?
’CAUSE, LIKE, YOU’RE EARLY.
( Alice sighs )
I’M NOT EARLY AT ALL.
I’M RIGHT ON TIME.
SINCE YOU HAVE
THE ENERGY TO WRESTLE,
MAYBE I SHOULD TELL
OLD MAN GARITTA
TO ADD SOME MORE SWINGS
TO YOUR DAILY QUOTA.
Kirito: NO, NOT THAT!
ANYTHING BUT THAT.
Alice: I’M JUST KIDDING.
- ( boys sigh )
- Alice: HERE.
IT’S TIME YOU HAD SOME LUNCH.
( boys sigh )
Alice: IT’S SO HOT TODAY.
YOU BETTER EAT IT FAST
BEFORE IT SPOILS.
Boys: OKAY!
Eugeo: MMM!
THE PIE SURE TASTES GOOD TODAY.
Kirito: MM-HMM.
ALICE, YOUR COOKING KEEPS
GETTING BETTER, FOR REAL.
( Alice gasps )
O-OH, I DON’T KNOW.
IT TURNED OUT OKAY, I GUESS,
BUT IT COULD HAVE BEEN BETTER.
( boys laugh )
Kirito: YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF ANYTHING, I WISH WE COULD
TAKE OUR TIME EATIN’ THIS,
INSTEAD OF RUSHIN’.
WHY DOES FOOD HAVE TO SPOIL
SO FAST WHEN IT’S HOT?
Eugeo: HEH. ’CAUSE IT’S HOT.
Kirito: I KNOW THAT,
BUT IN WINTER,
WE LEAVE RAW MEAT OUT,
AND IT KEEPS FOR DAYS,
AS LONG AS IT’S SALTED.
Eugeo: WELL, YEAH. THAT’S
’CAUSE IT’S COLD IN WINTER.
Kirito: THAT’S RIGHT!
AND IF WE COULD KEEP FOOD COLD
IN SUMMER, TOO,
IT WOULD LAST WAY LONGER!
Eugeo: BUT TO MAKE IT SNOW,
YOU’D HAVE TO USE THE FORBIDDEN
WEATHER-ALTERING ARTS TO.
THEN AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT
FROM THE AXIOM CHURCH
WOULD COME AND TAKE YOU AWAY.
( Kirito sighs )
ICE. THAT’S IT!
- Eugeo: HUH?
- Kirito: DON’T YOU SEE?
IF WE HAD LOTS OF ICE,
WE COULD KEEP THE FOOD COLD.
THEN WE COULD TAKE OUR TIME
AND ENJOY ALICE’S LUNCHES!
I SAY WE GO
HAVE OURSELVES A QUEST!
A QUEST FOR ICE.
Alice: HONESTLY...
IT’S SUMMER NOW.
WHERE WOULD YOU FIND ICE
THIS TIME OF YEAR?
EVEN THE MARKET
AT CENTORIA’S OUT.
Kirito: UH...
( sighs )
( groans )
WAIT. REMEMBER THAT STORY
ABOUT ONE OF
THE VILLAGE FOUNDERS, BERCOULI?
- Eugeo: EH?
- Alice: WHICH STORY?
Kirito: YOU KNOW, "BERCOULI AND
THE NORTHERN WHITE DRAGON."
♪
HE FOLLOWED THE RUL RIVER
ALL THE WAY TO ITS SOURCE,
A CAVE AT THE FOOT
OF THE END MOUNTAINS.
HE WENT IN AND
FOUND A PILE OF TREASURE
WITH A BIG WHITE DRAGON
SLEEPING ON TOP.
THEN HE GRABBED A SWORD
STICKING OUT OF THE TREASURE,
AND THE DRAGON WOKE UP.
( dragon roars )
Kirito: THE STORY ALSO SAYS
HE SAW GIANT ICICLES
A LITTLE WAYS
PAST THE MOUTH OF THE CAVE.
I SAY WE GO AND GET ’EM.
Eugeo: THAT’S CRAZY.
Alice: THAT’S NOT A BAD IDEA.
Eugeo: WAIT. YOU, TOO?!
COME ON. YOU KNOW
THE LAW OF THE VILLAGE.
- IT SAYS WE CAN’T--
- Alice: YES, I KNOW IT.
IT SAYS KIDS AREN’T ALLOWED
TO PLAY ANYWHERE
NEAR THE END MOUNTAINS,
UNLESS THEY HAVE
A GROWN-UP WITH THEM, BUT...
IF WE’RE THERE LOOKING FOR ICE,
THAT’S NOT PLAYING.
IF OUR VILLAGE HAD ICE,
ALL THE FOOD WOULD LAST LONGER,
AND THAT WOULD BENEFIT EVERYONE,
SO IF WE WENT TO GET SOME,
IT’D BE CONSIDERED WORK,
NOT PLAY.
Kirito: MM-HMM, SHE’S RIGHT.
IT’D TOTALLY BE WORK.
Eugeo: MAYBE, BUT WE
WOULDN’T JUST BE BREAKING
THE VILLAGE’S LAW
BY GOING UP THERE.
WE’D BE BREAKING
THE OTHER ONE, TOO.
Kirito: WHAT?
Eugeo: DON’T PLAY DUMB.
THE TABOO INDEX.
- ( both gasp )
- Eugeo: NO ONE’S ALLOWED
TO GO AGAINST THAT
FOR ANY REASON.
Alice: YOU’RE RIGHT,
BUT HERE’S WHAT IT SAYS
ABOUT THE END MOUNTAINS.
IN BOOK ONE,
CHAPTER THREE, VERSE 11,
THE INDEX SAYS "NONE SHALL
CROSS THE END MOUNTAINS
THAT SURROUND
THE HUMAN EMPIRE."
BY "CROSS," IT MEANS
ENTERING THE DARK TERRITORY
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE END MOUNTAINS.
IT DOESN’T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT GOING IN THE CAVE.
Eugeo: YEAH, BUT...
OW!
Kirito: THAT SETTLES IT!
THIS WEEKEND,
WE’LL FIND THAT DRA--
UH, I MEAN FIND THAT ICE CAVE.
Alice: OKAY.
LET’S MEET
IN THE MORNING AT 7:00
BY THE NORTH GATE.
Kirito: YOU GOT IT!
AND DON’T OVERSLEEP.
Alice: OH, PLEASE!
♪
( Alice humming )
Kirito: MAKING US
CARRY EVERYTHING.
WHO DOES SHE THINK WE ARE,
HER SERVANTS?
Eugeo: STOP COMPLAINING.
BE HAPPY WE CAN STILL
GO AND DO STUFF WITH HER.
- THAT’LL END SOON.
- Kirito: WHY?
Eugeo: SHE’S THE VILLAGE ELDER’S
DAUGHTER, THAT’S WHY.
SHE HAS TO LEARN ALL THAT STUFF
A LADY’S SUPPOSED TO KNOW,
LIKE MANNERS AND ETIQUETTE.
Kirito: YEAH,
AND SINCE SHE WASN’T
GIVEN A CALLING LIKE WE WERE,
SHE HAS TO STUDY ALL THOSE
SACRED ART SKILLS, TOO.
Eugeo: SHE’S GOING TO BE
A ROLE MODEL FOR THE VILLAGERS.
THAT MEANS NO MORE PLAYING
WITH US BOYS ANY MORE.
Alice: ALL RIGHT,
WHAT ARE THE TWO OF YOU
WHISPERING ABOUT BACK THERE?
Kirito: HUH? UM, NOTHING! RIGHT?
Eugeo: R-RIGHT.
WE WERE JUST SAYING
HOW WE’D GET IN TROUBLE
IF WE DON’T MAKE IT BACK
BEFORE THE EVENING BELL.
Alice: OH.
GOOD POINT.
THEN KEEP AN EYE ON SOLUS,
AND WHEN IT’S IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE SKY, WE’LL HEAD BACK.
COME ON, GUYS.
BACK TO OUR QUEST!
Boys: UH...
( both chuckle )
Kirito: WE’RE PRETTY FAR
FROM THE VILLAGE NOW.
DID YOU KNOW,
BACK IN THE OLDEN DAYS,
BACK WHEN RULID
WAS FIRST FOUNDED,
GOBLINS AND ORCS CAME DOWN
FROM THE DARK TERRITORY,
RAIDED THE VILLAGE, AND STOLE
A BUNCH OF SHEEP AND KIDS?
Alice: LISTEN, IF YOU’RE
TRYING TO SCARE ME, STOP IT.
I KNOW THE STORY.
AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT
CAME FROM CENTORIA
AND CHASED THEM ALL AWAY
IN THE END.
Kirito: THAT’S RIGHT,
AND, EVER SINCE,
ON CLEAR DAYS, YOU’LL SEE
A SILVER DRAGON KNIGHT
SOARING ABOVE THE END MOUNTAINS,
EVER VIGILANT!
( both gasp )
Kirito: HMM?
Alice: WE ALL SAW THAT, RIGHT?
( gasps )
IT’S THE CAVE.
WE REACHED THE END MOUNTAINS.
LET’S GO IN. IT’S WHY
WE CAME HERE, AFTER ALL.
SYSTEM CALL.
GENERATE LUMINOUS ELEMENT.
ADHERE.
( boys gasp )
♪
( footsteps echoing )
Eugeo: WELL, I DON’T SEE
ANY ICICLES YET.
DIDN’T YOU SAY THEY WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE A LITTLE WAYS IN?
Kirito: I DON’T KNOW. DID I?
- Eugeo: YOU DID!
- Kirito: HUH.
( gasps )
Alice: EUGEO.
Eugeo: YEAH?
Alice: COULD YOU PLEASE
BRING THAT LIGHT OVER HERE?
Eugeo: WHOA!
Alice: SEE THAT?
IT’S COLDER NOW.
Kirito: YOU’RE RIGHT.
IT TOTALLY IS.
FOR A SECOND THERE, I THOUGHT I
WAS COMING DOWN WITH SOMETHING.
Alice: IT’S KIND OF NEAT
HOW IT’S WINTER IN HERE,
BUT SUMMER OUTSIDE.
I BET WE’LL FIND SOME ICE
FURTHER IN.
Eugeo: YEAH. HOPEFULLY
NOT TOO MUCH FURTHER IN.
Alice: WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO
IF WE HAPPEN TO COME ACROSS
A WHITE DRAGON?
Eugeo: WE’LL RUN AWAY
AS FAST AS WE CAN.
Kirito: AH, QUIT WORRYIN’.
I SERIOUSLY DOUBT
IT’S GONNA MIND
IF WE TAKE A COUPLE ICICLES.
HMM. IT’D BE NEAT IF WE COULD
GRAB ONE OF ITS SCALES, THOUGH.
Eugeo: NO.
WE ARE NOT DOING THAT.
Kirito: WHY NOT?
HOW ELSE ARE WE GONNA PROVE
WE SAW A REAL, LIVE DRAGON?
( crackle )
- ( boys gasp )
- Alice: EH?
Eugeo: LOOK! IT’S ICE!
IT’S TRUE!
THERE’S ICE IN HERE!
Kirito: AND I BET YOU GUYS
THERE’S EVEN MORE UP AHEAD!
♪
Eugeo: SEE THAT?!
( gasps )
( Kirito gasps )
Alice: WITH THIS MUCH ICE,
WE CAN KEEP ALL THE FOOD
IN THE VILLAGE COLD.
Kirito: HECK,
WITH THIS MUCH ICE,
YOU CAN KEEP THE WHOLE
DANG VILLAGE COLD FOREVER.
Eugeo: JEEZ, WOULD YOU WATCH
WHERE YOU’RE GOING?
Kirito: EUGEO, LOOK.
Eugeo: EH?
( gasps )
Kirito: THERE IT IS.
( Alice gasps )
Kirito: WHOA.
Eugeo: THE DRAGON. NO WAY.
Alice: HOW DID IT DIE?
Kirito: LOOK. ITS CLAW’S
ALL COVERED IN GOUGES,
AND THEN IT WAS
CHOPPED CLEAN OFF.
Alice: THEN IT MUST HAVE
FOUGHT WITH SOMETHING.
BUT I DON’T KNOW OF ANYTHING
THAT COULD KILL A DRAGON.
Kirito: A SWORD
MADE THESE MARKS.
IT’S OBVIOUS WHAT KILLED IT,
A HUMAN.
( Eugeo gasps )
Alice: BUT WHO?
IF A SWORD-MASTER LIKE BERCOULI
COULDN’T FIGHT IT,
WHO’D BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO KILL IT?
( gasps )
AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT.
BUT WHY? THE WHITE DRAGONS
PROTECT OUR REALM.
WHY WOULD AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT
FROM THE AXIOM CHURCH KILL ONE?
Eugeo: WAIT A SECOND.
MAYBE THE DARK TERRITORY
HAS STRONG KNIGHTS, TOO,
AND ONE OF THEM KILLED IT.
IF THAT’S TRUE,
THEN THE ARMIES OF DARKNESS
COULD EASILY CROSS
THE END MOUNTAINS AND ATTACK US.
( gasps )
- ( Kirito grunting )
- Eugeo: WAIT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
Kirito: THIS IS HEAVIER
THAN IT LOOKS.
( grunting )
( Alice gasps )
IS THAT THE SWORD?
Kirito: YEAH, THE SAME ONE
BERCOULI TRIED TO STEAL,
THE BLUE ROSE SWORD.
( sighs )
( grunting )
IT’S TOO HEAVY.
I CAN’T LIFT IT.
EVEN WITH EUGEO’S HELP, WE’D
NEVER CARRY THIS BACK TO TOWN.
THERE’S A BUNCH OF OTHER
TREASURE WE COULD TAKE, THOUGH.
Alice: MM-HMM.
BUT SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
DOESN’T FEEL RIGHT.
IT WOULD BE LIKE GRAVE ROBBING.
Kirito: YEAH,
I GUESS YOU’RE RIGHT.
WE’LL JUST TAKE ICE.
THE DRAGON WON’T MIND THAT.
Alice: HOW PRETTY!
IT’S A SHAME IT’S
JUST GOING TO END UP MELTING.
Kirito: I COULDN’T CARE LESS,
AS LONG AS IT
MAKES OUR MEALS LAST LONGER.
Alice: NOT JUST OUR MEALS,
EVERYONE’S.
Eugeo: WE SHOULD START
HEADING BACK NOW,
OR ELSE WE WON’T MAKE IT
TO TOWN BEFORE DARK.
Alice: YOU’RE RIGHT.
( ice crackling )
WAIT.
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHICH TUNNEL WE CAME IN FROM?
WE’VE BEEN WALKING A LONG TIME.
IS THIS THE RIGHT TUNNEL,
OR WAS IT THE OTHER?
Kirito: SERIOUSLY?
WE PICKED THIS ONE
’CAUSE YOU SAID WE SHOULD.
Alice: WHAT? I DIDN’T HEAR YOU.
Kirito: UH, NEVER MIND.
( breeze blowing )
Eugeo: SHH.
- Kirito: EH?
- ( Alice gasps )
( shudders )
IS THAT THE WIND?
Eugeo: YOU PICKED
THE RIGHT PATH!
WE’RE ALMOST TO THE ENTRANCE!
Alice: WAIT! BE CAREFUL,
OR YOU’LL TRIP
AND HURT YOURSELF!
Eugeo: THERE IT IS!
♪
( Kirito sighs ) WHERE ARE WE?
Alice: THE DARK TERRITORY.
Eugeo: OH, NO.
W-WE BETTER TURN AROUND.
- ( metal clashes )
- ( kids gasp )
♪
Alice: DRAGON KNIGHTS.
Kirito: THAT WHITE ONE,
THAT’S A REAL, LIVE
INTEGRITY KNIGHT, ISN’T IT?
Eugeo: UH-HUH, AND THE OTHER’S
FROM THE DARK TERRITORY.
( Kirito gasps )
( kids gasp )
♪
( Alice shudders )
Kirito: NO, WAIT!
Eugeo: ALICE!
( boys gasp )
( Alice gasps )
( memory ) IN BOOK ONE,
CHAPTER THREE, VERSE 11,
THE INDEX SAYS, "NONE SHALL
CROSS THE END MOUNTAINS
THAT SURROUND
THE HUMAN EMPIRE."
( Kirito gasps )
ALICE!
( Alice gasps )
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
Eugeo: DON’T WORRY, ALICE.
IT’S OKAY.
I MEAN, IT’S NOT LIKE
YOU LEFT THE CAVE.
YOU DIDN’T.
SHE DIDN’T, DID SHE?
KIRITO?
( humming )
( boys gasp )
Eugeo: WHAT’S THAT?
Stranger: A SINGULAR UNIT
HAS BEEN DETECTED.
TRACING ITS I.D.
COORDINATES FIXED.
REPORT COMPLETE.
Eugeo: WH-WHAT WAS THAT THING?
Kirito: I DON’T KNOW.
LET’S GET OUT OF HERE!
( kids panting )
Kirito: SO, GUYS...
WHERE ARE WE GONNA PUT THIS?
( Alice chuckles )
I’LL PUT THE ICE IN MY BASEMENT,
WHERE IT’S NICE AND COOL.
Eugeo: O-OKAY.
Kirito: SEE YA.
EH?
Alice: I THINK TOMORROW’S LUNCH
WILL BE THE BEST ONE YET.
Kirito: CAN’T WAIT!
Eugeo: M-ME NEITHER.
( Alice giggles )
♪
( Eugeo gasping )
( whimpers )
( stranger growls )
Eugeo: ALICE.
DON’T GO! ALICE!
ALICE!
( gasps )
( insects chirping )
( sighs )
( ax chops )
( Kirito exhales )
( Eugeo gasps )
( gasps )
AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT!
Kirito: YEAH. HE’S THE SAME ONE
FROM YESTERDAY.
OH, NO. ALICE.
Eugeo: HE’S COME FOR HER.
BUT HE CAN’T
TAKE HER AWAY FOR THAT!
Kirito: COME ON!
Eugeo: W-WAIT!
( townsfolk murmuring )
Eugeo: ALICE.
Alice: KIRITO. EUGEO.
Kirito: KEEP IT DOWN.
BETTER GET OUTTA HERE
BEFORE HE SEES YOU.
( townsfolk gasping )
Alice: IT’S MY FATHER.
Gasfut: I AM GASFUT ZUBERG.
THE ELDER OF THIS VILLAGE.
Deusolbert: I AM
DEUSOLBERT SYNTHESIS SEVEN,
THE AXIOM INTEGRITY KNIGHT
WHO OVERSEES THE NORTHERN
NORLANGARTH TERRITORY.
YOUR DAUGHTER, ALICE ZUBERG,
HAS DISOBEYED THE TABOO INDEX.
I SHALL TAKE HER WITH ME
TO ANSWER FOR HER CRIMES
AND BE EXECUTED.
( townsfolk murmuring )
( all gasping )
Deusolbert: TABOO INDEX,
BOOK ONE, CHAPTER THREE,
VERSE 11 STATES NONE SHALL
CROSS INTO THE DARK TERRITORY.
♪
( Alice whimpering )
Kirito: SIR KNIGHT!
A-ALICE NEVER SET FOOT
IN THE DARK TERRITORY!
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT! ALL SHE DID
WAS TOUCH THE GROUND!
IT WAS ONLY FOR A SECOND!
Deusolbert: THAT IS ENOUGH
TO CHARGE HER WITH THE CRIME.
Kirito: THEN WE’RE
JUST AS GUILTY AS SHE IS!
WE WERE RIGHT THERE WITH HER!
IF YOU TAKE HER
THEN TAKE US, TOO!
EUGEO, LISTEN.
I’M GONNA CHARGE HIM
WITH THE AX.
GRAB ALICE, AND RUN.
Eugeo: H-HOLD ON.
I DON’T--WE CAN’T--
Kirito: I DON’T CARE
WHAT HAPPENS.
HER LIFE’S MORE IMPORTANT
THAN SOME STUPID OLD RULES!
( Eugeo stammering )
♪
KIRITO!
Deusolbert: ESCORT THOSE
TWO CHILDREN FROM THE SQUARE.
Kirito: LET HER GO!
DON’T JUST STAND THERE!
GO HELP HER!
( Eugeo grunts )
( gasping )
Kirito: EUGEO!
GET THESE GUYS OFF ME!
COME ON! HURRY!
EUGEO!
( Eugeo stammering )
( Kirito grunts )
ALICE!
( gasps )
( sighs )
( sighing )
( Sinon panting )
♪
( trigger clicking )
( player gasps )
( Sinon chuckles )
♪
Klein: THIS TANEGASHIMA’S
FULL-AUTO!
Lisbeth: WHAT’S UP,
YOU P.K. JERKS?
LET’S SEE HOW FAST YOU RUN.
( Silica laughing )
Klein: COWARDS!
Sinon: YOU’RE UP! I’LL COVER!
( photon sword hums )
♪
Player #2:
ARE THOSE PHOTON SWORDS?
Player #3: TEAM A NEEDS BACKUP.
B AND C, HEAD TO GRID FOUR-SIX.
YOU HAVE PERMISSION
TO USE GRENADES.
Player #2: HEY, BOSS,
LET ME IN ON THIS.
Player #3: NO.
THIS OP’S ABOUT TO WIND DOWN.
JUST SIT BACK, AND WATCH.
( Kirito gasps )
( chuckles )
Asuna: I GOT THIS!
( Kirito yells )
( photon sword hums )
Kirito: DAMN IT.
( device chirps )
Player #3:
WELL, THAT’S THE END OF THAT.
ALL TEAMS, RETREAT.
GRID ONE-NINE’S TOO HOT.
Player #2: AW, WE COULD
HAVE KILLED ’EM ALL
IF WE STUCK WITH IT.
YOU SURE YOU WANNA
END THE DAY LIKE THIS, BOSS?
Player #3: THAT TEAM’S
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
FIGHTING THEM
WON’T HELP WITH OUR TRAINING.
WE HAVE A BIG MISSION COMING UP,
AND WE NEED TO STAY SHARP.
LET’S GO.
Player #2: ’TIL NEXT TIME, KID.
Klein: OH, MAN, I HEARD "G.G.O."
WAS GONNA BE HARD-CORE,
BUT THAT WAS INSANE!
I NEVER PLAYED A GAME
WHERE IT’S COOL
JUST TO RUN AROUND AND KILL.
Sinon: ACTUALLY THERE’S A METHOD
TO THE MADNESS OF P.K.ing HERE.
YOU GO AFTER OTHER PLAYERS
FOR THEIR CASH OR ITEMS.
BUT THE TEAM WE JUST FOUGHT
DIDN’T CARE ABOUT THAT STUFF.
Kirito: YEAH, THE ONLY THING
THOSE GUYS WANTED
WAS TO STRAIGHT-UP KILL US.
AND DID YOU SEE ALL THE GRENADES
AND SMOKE BOMBS THEY USED?
ISN’T THAT STUFF EXPENSIVE?
Sinon: YOU KNOW IT.
AND THAT’S HOW THEY FIGHT
EVERY SINGLE TIME THEY SHOW UP.
THEY GO AFTER TEAMS THAT ARE
OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE,
MASSACRE EVERYONE,
THEN DISAPPEAR
WITHOUT LOOTING ANYONE.
Asuna: I SAW THEIR STATS.
IS IT TRUE THEY’VE
NEVER LOST A BATTLE?
Sinon: YEAH, IT’S TRUE.
THEY HAVEN’T.
STILL...
I THOUGHT IF ANYONE
COULD BEAT ’EM, WE COULD,
’CAUSE AS A TEAM,
WE’RE NOT LIKE ANYONE
THEY’VE COME UP AGAINST YET.
OH, WELL. I GUESS
IT JUST WASN’T IN THE CARDS.
I DIDN’T EXPECT THEY’D RETREAT.
THAT’S FOR SURE.
Klein: HEY, NO BIGGIE.
IT’S NOT LIKE WE LOST.
BESIDES, THEY RAN,
SO THAT’S A WIN IN MY BOOK.
Lisbeth: THE POINT WAS
TO FIND OUT WHO THEY WERE
AND WHAT THEY WERE
UP TO, TOUGH GUY.
Klein: YEAH, WELL,
A WIN’S A WIN.
Asuna: THAT SAID,
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN NICE
TO FIND OUT THE LEADER’S NAME.
Silica: YEAH, BUT WITH
THE WAY THEY FOUGHT,
IT WASN’T EVEN CLEAR
WHO THE LEADER WAS.
( Lisbeth yelps )
HEY, DON’T FLOP ON ME!
WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE, A PILLOW?
Asuna: HE SAID HE’S BEEN
TAKING TIME OFF FROM SCHOOL
SINCE THURSDAY
AND TOURING COMPANIES.
Sinon: KNOWING HIM,
HE’S PROBABLY MIXED UP
IN SOMETHING SINISTER AGAIN.
( Kirito sighing )
Sinon: THANKS AGAIN FOR HELPING
ME OUT, GUYS. YOU’RE THE BEST.
Klein: NO PROBS. ANYTIME!
LATER.
Silica: TODAY WAS FUN!
Lisbeth: SEE YA!
Asuna: WELL, BYE.
- Sinon: NO, WAIT. ONE SEC.
- Asuna: WHAT’S UP?
Sinon: I WAS HOPING YOU GUYS
COULD HELP ME WITH SOMETHING.
Asuna: THAT SQUAD OF P.K.ers?
Sinon: NO,
IT’S SOMETHING ELSE, ACTUALLY.
IF YOU AND KIRITO HAVE TIME,
COULD WE MEET I.R.L. TOMORROW?
Asuna: I THINK SO.
YEAH, I’M FREE IN THE EVENING.
DO YOU WANT TO MEET AT AGIL’S?
Sinon: SURE.
OH, I’LL ALSO
EMAIL YOU THE PLAN
SO YOU CAN THINK ABOUT IT,
IF THAT’S OKAY.
Asuna: SOUNDS GOOD.
( Kirito gasps )
Sinon: YOU’RE SO THIN.
ARE YOU EATING?
Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU, MY MOM?
ANYWAY, WHAT IS IT
YOU WANTED TO ASK ME?
IS IT ABOUT B.o.B.?
Sinon: MM-HMM.
THERE’S A PLAYER
CALLING HIMSELF SUBTILIZER,
WHO WON B.o.B. FOUR.
HE’S THE SAME GUY
WHO WON THE FIRST B.o.B.
Kirito: HUH.
Sinon: WHEN WE FOUND OUT
HE WAS IN FOUR,
EVERYONE GOT EXCITED, ’CAUSE
HE’S LIKE A LEGEND, YOU KNOW?
Kirito: YEAH. WE ALL
WATCHED THE LIVE FEED.
CAN’T BELIEVE HE STARTED
WITH JUST HIS BARE HANDS.
HE FOUGHT WITH A CONFIDANT,
STEALTHY STYLE,
LIKE THAT TEAM
FROM THE OTHER DAY.
Sinon: THEY DID HAVE
THE SAME VIBE, DIDN’T THEY?
WELL, EXCEPT SUBTILIZER’S ON
A WHOLE ’NOTHER LEVEL THAN THEM.
( sighs )
HE KILLED ME SO FAST.
I DIDN’T EVEN HAVE TIME TO AIM.
THAT’S HOW IT WAS
FOR EVERYONE IN THE TOURNEY.
IT’S LIKE HE KNEW OUR MOVES
BEFORE WE DID.
Kirito: NO WAY. REALLY?
BUT YOU’RE ALL VETS AT B.o.B.
HOW COULD HE ANTICIPATE
EVERYONE’S MOVES LIKE THAT?
Sinon: I SUPPOSE, AS VETS,
THERE’S A PREDICTABILITY
TO HOW WE PLAY.
WE TEND TO USE THE SAME MOVES,
’CAUSE THEY WORK.
WHICH BRINGS ME
TO WHY YOU’RE HERE.
( Kirito sighs )
Sinon: I WAS THINKING
THAT A PLAYER
WITH A MORE CHAOTIC
FIGHTING STYLE
MIGHT HAVE A BETTER CHANCE
AT OUTMANEUVERING SUBTILIZER.
ANYWAY, THE POINT
IS THE NEXT B.o.B.’S
GONNA BE HAPPENING
AT THE END OF THE YEAR,
AND I’D LIKE YOU
TO SIGN UP FOR IT.
Kirito: HUH? UH...
Sinon: THERE’S NO WAY
I’M GONNA LET MYSELF LOSE
TO THE SAME GUY AGAIN.
HE’S GOING DOWN.
Kirito: LOOKS LIKE
YOU MADE SOME PROGRESS.
Sinon: O-OH, YEAH.
I STILL GET THE SHAKES
EVERY NOW AND THEN,
BUT I’M GETTING BETTER.
Kirito: AND YOUR FRIEND,
IS HE DOING ANY BETTER?
( Sinon sighs )
YOU MEAN SHINKAWA.
YEAH, HE’S MAKING PROGRESS.
I’LL PROBABLY GO VISIT HIM
AGAIN IN A COUPLE DAYS.
Kirito: THAT’S GOOD.
WELL, LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
HE’S FINALLY GETTING THE HELP
HE NEEDS. DEATH GUN’S OVER.
Sinon: NO, IT ISN’T.
HIS PARTNER’S
STILL OUT THERE, REMEMBER?
Kirito: YEAH, BUT KIKUOKA SAID
THEY’LL CATCH UP WITH HIM
SOON ENOUGH.
Sinon: YEAH, I HOPE SO.
- ( entry bell rings )
- Asuna: WHEW. SORRY I’M LATE!
HEY THERE, SHINONON!
Kirito: WHAT’D YOU
JUST CALL HER?
Sinon: HEY, ASUNA.
RIGHT ON TIME.
Asuna: I READ YOUR EMAIL
ABOUT B.o.B. FIVE. I’M IN.
Kirito: WAIT.
YOU ASKED HER TO HELP, TOO?
Sinon: YUP. I FIGURED
IF IT WERE JUST YOU,
THERE’S A CHANCE
YOU’D GET TOO AGGRO.
EVEN GOOD DOGS
NEED A LEASH, RIGHT?
Kirito: DANG.
Asuna: HEY, KIRITO.
YOU’RE SO THIN. ARE YOU EATING?
Kirito: YEAH, I AM.
Sinon: HAH! SEE?
SHE CAN EVEN TELL
SOMETHING’S UP.
Asuna: IT’S THAT PART-TIME JOB,
ISN’T IT?
HONESTLY.
Kirito: UH...
Asuna: PHYSICALLY,
YOU’RE FINE, SO FAR.
Sinon: WAIT. YOU CAN TELL?
EH?
WHAT’S THAT?
Kirito: IT’S EXACTLY
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
Sinon: HUH?! YOU MEAN
SHE CAN TRACK YOUR VITALS?!
Asuna: NEAT, HUH?
Sinon: YEAH, I GUESS,
BUT, LIKE, HOW’S IT WORK?
Kirito: A LITTLE WHILE AGO,
I HAD THIS MINIATURE SENSOR
IMPLANTED IN MY CHEST.
IT SENDS MY HEART RATE,
BODY TEMPERATURE,
AND OTHER STUFF OVER THE NET
TO ASUNA’S SMARTPHONE.
Sinon: WHAT?!
WH-WHY WOULD YOU WANNA DO--
OH, I GET IT.
IT’S AN ANTI-CHEATING SYSTEM.
- Kirito: NO! NOT EVEN!
- Asuna: NO! NOT EVEN!
Kirito: WHEN I STARTED
THIS PART-TIME JOB,
THEY THOUGHT
IT’D BE GOOD TO GET IT.
I HAVE TO WEAR ELECTRODES,
AND STICKING ’EM ON
AND PULLING ’EM OFF’S
KIND OF A HASSLE.
USING IT LIKE THIS WAS HER IDEA,
SO I MADE A LITTLE APP FOR IT.
Asuna: YEAH, SOMETHING
ABOUT LOOKING AT IT’S
KIND OF SOOTHING,
KNOWING THAT’S KIRITO’S HEART
BEATING. ( sighs )
I GET ALL WOOZY,
AND MY HEAD STARTS TO SPIN.
( Kirito sighs, chuckles )
Sinon: UH, THAT’S BOTH CUTE
AND KINDA CREEPY.
A-ANYWAY, WITH YOU ON MY SIDE,
I’LL HAVE A MACHINE GUN
IN MY PILLBOX.
YOU’RE EXACTLY THE EDGE I NEED.
Asuna: I’M HAPPY TO HELP
ANY WAY I CAN.
( Kirito chuckles )
- Sinon: NOW, THEN...
- Kirito: WHAT?
Sinon: I WANNA HEAR SOME MORE
ABOUT THIS SKETCHY
NEW JOB OF YOURS.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU’RE ALPHA TESTING
A NEW V.R.M.M.O. GAME, RIGHT?
Kirito: ACTUALLY,
IT’S NOT A GAME.
IT’S A BRAIN-MACHINE INTERFACE
DESIGNED FOR THIS
BRAND-NEW FULL-DIVE SYSTEM.
RATH DEVELOPED IT.
THEY’RE NEW.
Sinon: WHAT THE HECK
KIND OF A NAME IS "RATH"?
Asuna: IT’S THE NAME
OF AN IMAGINARY CREATURE.
I REMEMBER IT FROM THE BOOK
"THROUGH THE LOOKING-GLASS."
SOME CHARACTERS SAID IT WAS
A PIG, AND OTHERS, A TURTLE.
Sinon: SO ARE THEY RELEASING
SOME NEXT-GEN FULL-DIVE RIG
FOR GAMING?
Kirito: I DON’T KNOW. MAYBE.
THIS THING’S TOTALLY DIFFERENT
COMPARED TO THE FULL-DIVE TECH
THAT’S OUT NOW.
Sinon: OH. SO WHAT’S
THE IN-GAME WORLD LIKE?
- Kirito: I HAVE NO IDEA.
- Sinon: HUH?
Kirito: IT’S HOW THEY
KEEP THINGS CONFIDENTIAL.
THE MEMORIES I MAKE USING
THEIR RIG IN THE V.R. WORLD,
THEY DON’T STICK WITH ME
IN THE REAL WORLD.
WHATEVER I SAW DURING THE TESTS,
WHATEVER I DID,
I FORGET ALL OF IT
AFTER I LOG OUT.
- Sinon: UH, HUH?!
- ( Asuna gasps )
Sinon: YOU CAN’T REMEMBER
ANYTHING AT ALL?
OH, MY GOD.
IS IT ANOTHER AUGMA?
Kirito: UH, N-NO.
IT’S NOT LIKE THAT!
THIS RIG DOESN’T PUT STRESS ON
YOUR BRAIN LIKE THE AUGMA DID.
I DIDN’T LOSE MY MEMORIES
OR ANYTHING.
I JUST CAN’T ACCESS THEM
FROM MY FLUCTLIGHT.
- Sinon: UH...
- Asuna: A FLUCT WHAT?
Kirito: THIS IS GONNA
TAKE SOME TIME TO EXPLAIN.
FIRST OFF,
THE RIG I’M TESTING’S
CALLED THE SOUL TRANSLATOR.
WHERE IN YOUR BODY
DO YOU THINK YOUR SOUL IS?
Asuna: SERIOUSLY?
Sinon: I DON’T KNOW.
IN THE BRAIN?
Kirito: IF YOU ZOOM IN
TO THE BRAIN,
YOU’LL SEE
IT’S MADE UP OF CELLS.
SO WHERE IN ALL THOSE CELLS
DO YOU THINK THE SOUL IS?
Sinon: I-I DON’T KNOW.
Kirito: ZOOM IN TO A BRAIN CELL,
AND YOU’LL SEE
THAT IT HAS THINGS IN IT
THAT SUPPORT
THE CELL’S STRUCTURE.
THEY’RE CALLED MICROTUBULES.
Sinon: OKAY.
Kirito: LIKE THE NAME IMPLIES,
THEY’RE LIKE HOLLOW PIPES,
BUT THEY’RE NOT EMPTY.
THEY GOT SOMETHING
SEALED INSIDE.
Sinon: SO WHAT
DO THEY HAVE INSIDE?
Kirito: LIGHT.
THAT’S IT, FLUCTUATING LIGHT.
IT’S THE BUILDING BLOCK
OF THE HUMAN SOUL,
ACCORDING TO RATH.
Asuna: SO LET ME SEE
IF I UNDERSTAND THIS.
THEY’RE SAYING THIS LIGHT
IN BRAIN CELLS, THAT’S THE SOUL?
Kirito: YEAH.
THEY DON’T CALL IT
A SOUL AT RATH, THOUGH.
THEY DECIDED TO GO
WITH A COMBINATION
OF THE WORDS "FLUCTUATING"
AND "LIGHT,"
"FLUCTLIGHT" FOR SHORT.
Sinon: HUH.
Asuna: THEN THE SOUL TRANSLATOR
DOESN’T JUST READ
A PERSON’S BRAIN.
IT READS THEIR FLUCTLIGHT.
WHICH MEANS IT CAN
ALSO IMPRINT ON THEM.
Sinon: IMPRINT?
Asuna: LIKE THE AMUSPHERE.
THAT RIG LETS YOU EXPERIENCE
V.R. BY SENDING IMAGES,
SOUNDS, AND OTHER SENSORY
INFORMATION TO YOUR BRAIN.
WITH THIS RIG,
SINCE IT’S NEXT-GEN AND ALL,
IT WOULD WORK THE SAME WAY,
BUT ON YOUR SOUL, RIGHT?
Kirito: YEAH, THAT’S RIGHT.
THE NAME
PRETTY MUCH SAYS IT ALL.
THE SOUL TRANSLATOR, OR S.T.L.,
WRITES SHORT-TERM MEMORIES
ONTO YOUR FLUCTLIGHT
OF THE SIGHTS AND SOUNDS
IT WANTS YOU TO EXPERIENCE.
MNEMONIC VISUAL DATA
IS WHAT IT’S CALLED.
I REMEMBER THE TEST DIVES I TOOK
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE JOB.
( note vibrates )
THOSE DIVES WERE DIFFERENT.
I WAS BLOWN AWAY.
IT’S NOTHING LIKE
WHAT THE AMUSPHERE CREATES.
EVERYTHING WAS SO REAL,
I COULDN’T TELL IT WAS
A VIRTUAL WORLD AT FIRST.
Asuna: I DON’T KNOW.
THIS SCARES ME.
I MEAN, IS IT SAFE?
MR. KIKUOKA OFFERED YOU THE JOB,
AND THAT’S GREAT,
BUT WHO KNOWS
WHAT HIS MOTIVES ARE?
( Kirito sighs )
YEAH, YOU’RE RIGHT,
BUT I DON’T LET MY GUARD DOWN
AROUND HIM EVER.
THE THING IS I WANNA KNOW.
I HAVE TO DO THIS TO SEE
WHERE FULL-DIVE’S HEADING.
I KNOW IT’S RISKY,
BUT THE S.T.L.’S SPECIAL.
SURE TERMS LIKE "MNEMONIC"
AND "FLUCTLIGHT" SOUND CREEPY,
BUT I CONNECT WITH IT.
WAY MORE THAN THE AMUSPHERE.
IT’S LIKE A WAKING DREAM
WHEN I’M IN IT.
Asuna: HOW SO?
Kirito: YOU KNOW
HOW YOU SOMETIMES HAVE DREAMS
THAT SEEM LONG,
THE KIND WHERE YOU WAKE UP
AND YOU’D SWEAR THAT DREAM
WENT ON FOR HOURS,
ESPECIALLY IF IT
WAS A NIGHTMARE?
THE TRUTH IS, THAT DREAM
PROBABLY ONLY LASTED
A FEW MINUTES.
YOU GET THAT SAME PHENOMENA
IF YOU DIVE WITH THE S.T.L.
Sinon: SERIOUSLY?
Kirito: IT’S JUST LIKE A DREAM
THAT FELT LIKE HOURS,
BUT WAS ONLY A FEW MINUTES.
YOUR TIME DIVING WITH THE S.T.L.
IS WAY LONGER THAN YOUR DIVE.
( Sinon gasps )
Kirito: THAT’S THE MAIN FEATURE
OF THE S.T.L.
RATH CALLS IT
FLUCTLIGHT ACCELERATION,
OR F.L.A. FOR SHORT.
Sinon: WHOA.
Asuna: I’M SO CONFUSED.
Sinon: MY HEAD’S SPINNING.
YOU WERE DIVING
FOR THREE WHOLE DAYS,
SO HOW MUCH TIME
WAS THAT IN V.R.?
Kirito: MM, I’M NOT SURE.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN TEN DAYS
OR A MONTH.
I DON’T REMEMBER HOW LONG.
WHEN I ASKED HOW LONG,
THEY WOULDN’T TELL ME,
BUT THEY DID TELL ME
THE CODE NAME OF THE TEST WORLD.
Sinon: REALLY? WHAT IS IT?
Kirito: THE UNDERWORLD.
Sinon: SO IT’S LIKE
AN UNDERGROUND WORLD?
Asuna: IT’S A REFERENCE.
IT HAS TO DO WITH "ALICE,"
SAME AS RATH.
"ALICE IN WONDERLAND"
WAS THE TITLE
THE BOOK WAS PUBLISHED UNDER,
BUT IT HAD A DIFFERENT TITLE
WHEN IT WAS BEING WRITTEN.
ORIGINALLY IT WAS CALLED
"ALICE’S ADVENTURES
UNDER GROUND."
( Kirito sighs )
Sinon: YOU OKAY?
Kirito: WHEN I HEARD
THE NAME "ALICE,"
IT FELT LIKE I WAS
ABOUT TO REMEMBER SOMETHING.
Sinon: SOMETHING ABOUT THE TEST?
Kirito: I’M NOT SURE.
IT FEELS LIKE
THERE’S SOMETHING I NEED TO DO.
I JUST CAN’T REMEMBER WHAT.
( Asuna sighs )
Sinon: THANKS, AGIL.
SEE YOU LATER!
- Agil: BYE, GUYS!
- ( entry bell rings )
Sinon: I’LL KEEP YOU GUYS
UP TO DATE ABOUT B.o.B.
THANKS AGAIN
FOR MEETING UP WITH ME TODAY.
Asuna: SURE!
SEE YOU LATER, SHINONON!
Sinon: SEE YOU.
Asuna: THAT WAS FUN.
EH?
WHAT’S WRONG?
Kirito: SAY WHAT?
OH. NOTHING.
♪
( sighs )
( Asuna sighs )
TALK TO ME.
Kirito: ASUNA...
I THINK I’M GONNA GO.
- Asuna: TO AMERICA?
- Kirito: YEAH.
THE RESEARCH IS
WAY MORE ADVANCED THERE.
IT’S ALL NEXT-GEN STUFF.
THEY’RE CREATING A NEW WORLD,
AND I WANNA BE THERE
WHEN IT’S BORN.
( Asuna chuckles )
WE WERE HAPPY IN AINCRAD.
BUT THERE WAS
SO MUCH PAIN AND SADNESS, TOO.
YOU WANT TO FIND OUT
WHY THAT CASTLE STILL
HAUNTS YOUR THOUGHTS
AND WHERE THAT EXPERIENCE
IS TAKING YOU.
Kirito: EVEN IF I LIVED
A COUPLE HUNDRED YEARS,
I DOUBT I’D EVER FIND THAT OUT.
ANYWAY, I-I WANT...
I WANT YOU WITH ME,
ASUNA, ALWAYS.
I WANT YOU TO COME WITH ME,
AND I-I KNOW THAT’S ASKING
A LOT, BUT THE TRUTH IS...
I CAN’T DO THIS WITHOUT YOU!
( Asuna gasps )
( sighs )
OF COURSE.
I’LL GO ANYWHERE WITH YOU.
IT DOESN’T MATTER WHERE.
I’LL GO.
Kirito: ASUNA.
( footsteps echoing )
Asuna: SO DOES THIS MEAN
THE SOUL TRANSLATOR
ISN’T THE NEXT STEP IN V.R.?
HEARING YOU TALK ABOUT IT,
I THOUGHT IT WAS.
Kirito: EH, I DON’T KNOW.
FOR SOME REASON,
I GET THE FEELING ITS PURPOSE
ISN’T JUST TO FULL-DIVE
IN V.R. WORLDS.
Asuna: THEN WHAT’S IT FOR?
Kirito: A TOOL FOR LEARNING
ABOUT FLUCTLIGHTS
AND HUMAN CONSCIOUSNESS.
Asuna: HMM?
Kirito: IT’S LIKE...
WHATEVER I KNOW ABOUT THE S.T.L.
MAKES ME THINK
IT MIGHT BE AN EXTENSION
OF KAYABA’S IDEAS.
( Asuna gasps )
HE’S BEHIND IT?!
Kirito: I DON’T KNOW WHY HE
MADE THE NERVEGEAR AND "S.A.O."
TO TRAP EVERYONE
AND MAKE US ALL SUFFER
OR WHY HE’D FRY HIS OWN BRAIN.
AND THE SEED, HE DIDN’T MAKE IT
JUST TO KEEP V.R. ALIVE.
I WANNA KNOW
WHAT HIS ENDGAME WAS,
BUT I DON’T WANT IT TO BE MINE.
I’M NOT HIS PUPPET,
AND IF I GO DOWN THAT ROAD,
I WOULD BE.
Asuna: YOU SAID
YOU TALKED TO HIM
OR THE PART OF HIM
HE LEFT BEHIND.
Kirito: YEAH.
I THINK I KNOW WHY HE LEFT
A COPY OF HIMSELF OUT THERE,
AND IT MIGHT
HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH WHAT RATH’S UP TO
WITH THE S.T.L.
- EH?
- Asuna: EH?
Man: HEY, SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
I’M SORTA LOST.
WHERE’S THE STATION?
Asuna: OH, JUST DOWN THERE.
KIRITO?
Kirito: YOU FOLLOWED US
FROM DICEY’S CAFE.
( man sighs )
THERE GOES MY PLAN
TO AMBUSH Y’ALL.
Kirito: WHO ARE YOU?
Man: AH, COME ON, KIRITO.
DON’T YOU RECOGNIZE ME?
OH. THAT’S RIGHT.
I ALWAYS WORE A MASK BACK THERE.
YEAH, NOW THAT
XAXA’S BEEN CAUGHT,
THERE’S NO ONE LEFT
TO FINISH THINGS BUT ME,
THE LAST SURVIVOR
OF LAUGHING COFFIN...
Kirito: JOHNNY BLACK!
( gasps )
( Johnny laughing )
YOU ASS! YOU GOT NO SWORD HERE!
Kirito: SO YOU’RE
STILL ON THE RUN?
Johnny: OF COURSE!
DAMN, KIRITO. ( laughs )
I CAN’T BELIEVE
YOU’RE THE SAME DUDE
THAT BEAT THE HELL OUTTA US!
BUT YOU’RE JUST A PUNK-ASS KID,
AIN’T YOU?
TAKE AWAY YOUR SWORDS,
AND YOU’RE NOTHING.
Kirito: WHAT ABOUT YOU?
YOU DON’T HAVE
YOUR POISON DAGGER.
Johnny: I DON’T?
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT, KIRITO?!
Kirito: DEATH GUN.
( Johnny laughing )
Kirito: RUN! GET OUTTA HERE!
- ( hypodermic hisses )
- ( Asuna gasps )
♪
( gasps )
( Kirito grunts )
Asuna: KIRITO!
♪
♪ SHINY SWORD, MY DIAMOND ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ IT’S TIME ♪